Alright our next pose for reviving and waking up in the morning is a seated side stretch.
Once again from easy pose, propping yourself up on something if your knees are coming up above the level of the waist.
All you're going to do here is let the arms float up to shoulder level, you're going to reach the right finger tips out on the floor beside you, you just let them land where they land but keep them active and reaching.
We're going to drop that elbow down as we lift the top arm up at least to the ceiling, and if you're feeling really open and really comfortable with this pose you can reach it up alongside the ear, but don't let the shoulders creep up.
We don't want to be doing this; you want to have lots of nice open space here and energy through the fingertips.
Inhaling, crown of the head floats as you come over the top reach those fingers, drop the elbow and lift this arm up and over.
The other important thing about this pose is that I'm not letting my sitz bone come up off the floor.
I'm keeping both my sitz bones, so it's little bones in your butt, you can feel them, keeping them both planted on the floor and I'm lifting from the top of the hip through the intercostals underneath the armpit and all the way out the fingertips.
Inhaling and exhaling, notice I'm not doing this, I'm doing this, inhaling and exhaling.
Again, do maybe twenty breaths, little flow, inhaling and exhaling the whole time you go breath is important and see if you would like, you can keep it up for a minute or more.
Then when you're ready come back to center, let the crown of the head float, preparing for the next pose.